<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mason</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_user_center">User Center</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="content">RESEARCH PROCEDURES: \n
        We invite you to participate in an important research study to gauge the effects of a digital
        health solution on students’ mental health and college success during the COVID-19
        pandemic. In the U.S., there have been more than 30 million COVID-19 infections and 600,000
        related deaths. The coronavirus has had a disastrous effect on the daily lives of Americans,
        adversely affecting education, employment, and mental wellbeing. This study will examine the
        utility of a data-driven and proactive app for undergraduate students’ academic success and
        mental well-being during the COVID-19 pandemic. The app will predict and contextualize
        retention rates by sensing for physical, behavioral, and emotional risk factors and may prompt
        higher education institutions to intervene with specific students at specific times for specific
        reasons. The app will be tailored to the wide diversity of students attending GMU, including low-income, minority, and under-represented populations. We expect that the study will take 45-50
        minutes of your time over the course of the semester. Your time will be spent reading the
informed consent document and completing weekly 3-minute-long surveys over the course of
the semester. Surveys will include questions on content such as academic goals, coping
strategies, and stress. \n
RISKS: \n
There are minimal foreseeable risks to participating in this study. You may skip over questions
you do not feel comfortable answering or withdraw at any time. You can also reach Counseling
and Psychological Services (CAPS) should you seek resources if you encounter
stress/discomfort while take the survey (703-993-2380). \n
BENEFITS: \n
There are no direct benefits to participants who partake in this study.\n
CONFIDENTIALITY: \n
The data in this study will be confidential. While it is understood that no computer transmission
can be perfectly secure, reasonable efforts are made to protect the confidentiality of your data
transmission. Data will be stored in one computer which will remain in Peterson Hall on the
Fairfax campus. Faculty included on this project will have access to your identifying information,
including your name, email, and George Mason University G number. Other researchers will
receive access to data in a de-identified format to ensure participant privacy and confidentiality.
CAPS and participants’ academic advisors may receive access to personal identifiers if deemed
necessary by this study’s researchers as well. De-identified data could be used for future
research without additional consent from you. The Institutional Review Board (IRB) committee
that monitors research on human subjects may inspect study records during internal auditing procedures and are required to keep all information confidential. If a participant indicates
immediate mental health issues or dropping grades within the app, CAPS and/or their academic
advisor will receive contact from research staff for an intervention. \n
        PARTICIPATION: \n
Your participation is voluntary, and you can refuse to answer questions in weekly surveys or
drop out at any time. We won’t associate any of your answers with you specifically. There are
no costs or foreseeable risks for you to take part in this study. You will receive $20 for the
completion of 8 weeks’ worth of surveys. Upon completing 8 weeks of surveys, you will be given
$2/week for continued participation in the app. You can earn a maximum of $36 for completing
each weekly survey. Note that you must reach 8 weeks of survey completions in order to
receive any compensation. All payouts will be distributed in Amazon e-gift cards. Under the U.S.
federal tax law, you may have individual responsibilities for disclosing the dollar value of the
incentive received on this study. \n
ELIGIBILITY: \n
You are considered eligible to participate in this study if you: \n
 - Are 18 years of age or older \n
 - Are a current undergraduate student at George Mason University \n
CONTACT: \n
This survey is being conducted by Lawrence Cheskin, MD and Alison Cuellar, PhD,
multidisciplinary professors at George Mason University. You can contact them at
lcheskin@gmu.edu and aevanscu@gmu.edu, respectively. Alternatively, you can reach
Lawrence Cheskin, PhD at 703-993-6264. You may also contact the George Mason University
Institutional Review Board office at 703-993-4121 or email irb@gmu.edu if you have questions
or comments regarding your rights as a participant. This research has been reviewed according
to George Mason University procedures governing your participation in this research. \n
CONSENT: \n
I have read this form, all my questions have been answered by the research staff, and I agree to
participate in this study. By selecting “yes,” I indicate my eligibility and consent to participate. </string>
    <string name="channel_name">channel_name</string>
    <string name="channel_description">channel_description</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ques7">Ques7Activity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
</resources>